QuestionList=[{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In Half-Life 2, if you play the zombies&#039; speech in reverse, they actually speak coherent English.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The Sniper&#039;s SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout&#039;s primary weapon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "TF2: The Medic will be credited for an assist if he heals a Spy that successfully saps a building.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]